Guide to the Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection MSS.158
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Manuscript Scores by Buddy Baker
  - Unidentified - Pit plot, notes, click layout - 1981, 1981Dec 7-8 (?); Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 37)
    notes, pit plot, click layout
  - Unidentified Autograph - Body and soul, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 12 (Box 38)
    autograph black pencil score on 14 stave yellow paper, Lockie Music Exchange, 950 South Broadway Los Angeles printed at bottom
  - Unidentified Autograph - Cuban Love Song (Box 38)
  - Unidentified Autograph - East of the son, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 38)
    autograph black pencil score on 12 stave yellow paper stamped Hollywood Music Papers
  - Unidentified Autograph - Guilty (Box 38)
  - Unidentified Autograph - Mood for Love (Box 38)
  - Unidentified Autograph (?) - Yankee Doodle, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 38)
    manuscript black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper annotated in black, red and green. Walt Disney Studio Music Dept. printed at bottom
  - Unidentified Autograph 1, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 73)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave and 22 stave score with red annotations; manuscript black pencil 15 stave full score with red annotations
  - Unidentified autograph sketches, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 37)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red annotations
    13B
    Sugar Plum Fairies; Reed flutes;It only takes a moment;Untitled;If you go away;Fanfare; Watch what happends
  - Unidentified Miscellaneous Notes, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 38)
    photocopies time footage computer, bagpipe part
    0108
  - Unidentified Photocopies - Orchestral parts 1 [Parts 1-3], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 38)
    photocopies orchestral parts
  - Unidentified Photocopy full score - Cues 1B-7F, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 38)
    1B-7F
  - Various manuscripts - Latin rhythms, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    autograph song; manuscript black pencil notes on Latin rhythms
  - Various Photocopies - Disneyland after dark, Zorro, etc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 9 (Box 33)
    photocopies copyist short score; photocopy manuscript notes on Scales
  - Various themes - Autograph sketches, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    autograph sketches on 10 and 12 stave yellow paper
  - Various Themes - Autograph sketches 2, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    autograph black pencil sketches on 10 and 12 stave yellow and white paper
  - Various themes - Autograph songs and short scores, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    autograph lead sheets and short scores
  - Various themes - Autographs 1-3, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 93)
    autograph black pencil sketches, short scores; photocopies: copyist short scores, autograph short scores; timing tables;typed lyrics
  - Various themes - Baker - Photocopies 1-4, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 94)
    photocopies of lead sheets and short scores
  - Various themes - Other Composers, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 93)
    photocopies copyist short scores, lead sheets
  - Various themes - Timing tables (Box 93)
  - Various themes - Typed lists of songs, synopses, etc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    photocopy songs; typed lists of songs;synopses Cowardly Lion of Oz; ms. Notes
  - Wahoo Bobcat - Autograph - 9 stave short score - Cues 1A-6F (Box 69)
  - Wahoo Bobcat - Order of takes, 1963 Aug 26-27; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 69)
    typed order of takes; autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    3112
    1A-6F
  - Walt Disney Story - Autograph short score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 34)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; storyboard in brown binder
    1A-3N,AA,BB
  - Walt Disney Story - Storyboard (Box 34)
  - Walt Disney World Show - A Walt Disney Show Case, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 69)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with green, blue, red and black annotations; photocopy conductor score
    Walt Disney Productions; Schaefer, Will
  - Walt Disney World Show - Kid Themes Autograph Sketches, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 35)
    autograph black pencil sketches, short score on 12 stave white and yellow paper with blue, green and red annotations
    1A-3Ev, songs 1-3,5-9,11,14-15
  - Walt Disney World Show - Piano Conductor, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 35)
    2520
    1A-4KV
  - Walt Disney World Show - The New Mickey Mouse Club, 1972 Oct 10-13; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 35)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; annotated music breakdown sheets, order of takes and orchestra recording schedule
    2520;8303
    1X-4L
  - When you wish upon a star, undated; Harline, Leigh (Box 94)
    autograph black pencil full score annotated in red,blue and green, 32 staves
    2fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,2bsn,4hn,3tpt,3tbn,organ,3perc,piano,harp,strings
  - Whisper in the Gloom - Annotated forms, 1979 Nov 14-16; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 36)
    annotated music breakdown sheets, order of takes and orchestra recording schedule;autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations; reduced photocopies of short score
    3903
  - Whisper in the Gloom - Autograph - Cues RQ1-10H (Box 36)
  - Whisper in the Gloom - photocopy - Short score (Box 36)
  - Wild Geeese Calling, 1969 Jul 29-31, Aug 4; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 37)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; annotated music breaddown sheets, order of takes and orchestra recording schedule
    3486
    1Av(x)-6Dv(1)
    Blair, Hal, 1915-2001; Sheets, Walter; Walt Disney Productions
  - Winnie the Pooh - Annotated copyist score - photocopy (Box 71)
  - Winnie the Pooh - Annotated forms, 1965 Mar 17, 24, Aug 4; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 70)
    autograph black pencil short score sketches on 12 stave white paper with red annotations;copyist composits sketch photocopy;annotated forms; autograph 9 stave score; photocopies score
    2515; 2504
    1A-3Tv2
  - Winnie the Pooh - Autograph score - Cues 1A-3TV2 (Box 70)
  - Winnie the Pooh - Autograph sketches short score (Box 70)
  - Winnie the Pooh - Copyist composite sketch photocopy, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 71)
    photocopy copyist short score with annotations;; photocopy piano conductor short score
    2504;2515
  - Winnie the Pooh - Photocopies - Cues 1A-3TV2 (Box 70)
  - Winnie the Pooh - Piano conductor - photocopy (Box 71)
  - Winnie the Pooh (Theme Park) - Autograph 9 stave scores 1 & 2 (Box 72)
  - Winnie the Pooh (Theme Park) - Autograph short score (Box 72)
  - Winnie the Pooh (Theme Park) - Notes, Floor Plans, etc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 7 (Box 72)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper;autograph sketch on 18 stave white paper; manuscript notes, floor plan, typed audio media scope, etc; autograph 9 stave score on 18 stave white paper; photocopy 9 stave score
  - Winnie the Pooh (Theme Park) - Photocopies - Songs (Box 72)
  - Winnie the Pooh (Theme Park) - Score - photocopy (Box 72)
  - Winnie the Pooh and Tigger too - Autographs, 1974 Sep 4-5; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 72)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with green, red and blue annotations; annotated music breakdown sheets, order of takes and orchestra recording schedule
    2518
    1F-3L
  - Silver Fox and Sam Davenport, The, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 66)
    autograph black pencil condensed score on 18 stave yellow paper with red and blue annotations
    5848
- Series II: Manuscript Scores by Others
  - Robert Brunner - Biscuit eater, undated; Brunner, Robert F.; 6 (Box 42)
    photocopy piano conductor, full scores
  - Riddle/Rugalo, undated; Riddle, Nelson (Box 42)
  - Geo. Wilkins et al., Epcot New Horizons American Journeys, undated; Wilkins, George; 3 (Box 43)
    photocopies of manuscript and printed music
  - Koff, Harmony - from The Science of Acoustics - manuscript notes, copy (Box 73)
  - Bernstein, Jarre, Raksin, Young - Society for the Preservation of Film Music Scores 1& 2, undated; 5 (Box 73)
    photocopy scores by Bernstein, Raksin, Jarre, Young
- Series III: Assorted Media
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Three Caballeros, The, 1945; ID: 158.0002 (Box 95, Vhs ID: 158.0002)
    Custodial History
    Originally stored with material from Box 61: Mexican Pavillion
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    TRT: 71:34
  - Sinbad "Finale" Demo Rev 1.0, ID: 158.0003 (Box 95, Audiocassette ID: 158.0003)
  - Mexico, undated; cuid41195 (Box 95, Audiocassette ID: 158.0004)
  - Puppetoon Movie, undated; ID: 158.0001 (Box 95, 35mm film reels ID: 158.0001)
    Gauge: 35 mm, black and white workprint
    Length: [800 feet]
    Leibovit Productions; Walt Disney Productions
- Series IV: Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous bound music and click books, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 40)
    bound music and click books
  - Miscellaneous Notes, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; no count (Box 39)
    Miscellaneous correspondence, class notes, typed and handwritten notes, and scores for music played at the 1964 World's Fair.
  - The Theory and Practice of click tracks. By Marc Fredericks, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 41)
    bound typescript click book; photographs/ contact sheet for American Adventure